ROOMS = {
	[0,0,0] => {
		room_number: 18,
		hint: 'You are on the right floor.',
		question: 'How many years did Rory wait on Amy while she was in the Pandorica?',
		answer: '1894',
	},
	[0,1,0] => {
		room_number: 13,
		hint: 'Going foward would be better than going backward.',
		question: "What is River Song's name at birth?",
		answer: 'melody pond',
	},
	[0,2,0] => {
		room_number: 9,
		hint: 'You are on the wrong side of the castle.',
		question: "In the episode 'Kill the Moon', what does the moon turn out to be?",
		answer: 'an egg',
	},
	[0,0,1] => {
		room_number: 15,
		hint: 'Go forward to find what you seek.',
		question: 'What is the name of the scientist who created the Daleks?',
		answer: 'davros',
	},
	[0,1,1] => {
		room_number: 19,
		hint: 'You are very close.',
		question: 'Where did the Doctor first meet River Song?',
		answer: 'the library',
	},
	[0,2,1] => {
		room_number: 16,
		hint: 'You are on the wrong side of the castle.',
		question: "What is the first name of the Doctor's companion who is an actual medical doctor?",
		answer: 'martha',
	},
	[0,0,2] => {
		room_number: 12,
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[0,1,2] => {
		room_number: 17,
		hint: 'Go left to find what you seek!',
		question: "What is the name of Rose Tyler's persona?",
		answer: 'bad wolf',
	},
	[0,2,2] => {
		room_number: 4,
		hint: 'Go left.',
		question: 'What is the first name of the companion the Doctor had to completely wipe the memories of?',
		answer: 'donna',
	},
	[1,0,0] => {
		room_number: 'courtyard',
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[1,1,0] => {
		room_number: 8,
		hint: "You're going the wrong way.",
		question: 'What planet do the Cybermen originate from?',
		answer: 'mondas',
	},
	[1,2,0] => {
		room_number: 2,
		hint: 'You are not on the right floor',
		question: "Clara Oswald is better known in 'Asylum of the Daleks' as what?",
		answer: 'souffle girl',
	},
	[1,0,1] => {
		room_number: 'room you started in',
		hint: '', 
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[1,1,1] => {
		room_number: "garden",
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[1,2,1] => {
		room_number: 'hall',
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[1,0,2] => {
		room_number: 7,
		hint: 'The rooms are not in order',
		question: 'What do the Daleks call the Doctor on their planet?',
		answer: 'the deadly traveler',
	},
	[1,1,2] => {
		room_number: 1,
		hint: 'There are 19 rooms in the castle, as well as a hall, a courtyard, a garden, and a kitchen. The garden, courtyard and hall all take up two floors.',
		question: "What is the name of Amy and Rory's daughter?",
		answer: 'river song',
	},
	[1,2,2] => {
		room_number: 'kitchen',
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[2,0,0] => {
		room_number: 'courtyard',
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[2,1,0] => {
		room_number: 3,
		hint: "You're getting colder.",
		question: 'What race from Doctor Who has shape-shifting abilities?',
		answer: 'zygons',
	},
	[2,2,0] => {
		room_number: 6,
		hint: 'If you move down a floor now, you will be in room 2, if you go down further you will be in room 9.',
		question: 'What corporation enslaved the Oods?',
		answer: 'ood operations',
	},
	[2,0,1] => {
		room_number: 11,
		hint: 'Go forward and what you need to do will be revealed.',
		question: 'What creatures are immediately forgotten after you stop looking at them?',
		answer: 'the silence',
	},
	[2,1,1] => {
		room_number: "garden",
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[2,2,1] => {
		room_number: 'hall',
		hint: '',
		question: '',
		answer: '',
	},
	[2,0,2] => {
		room_number: 5,
		hint: 'You are on top of what you seek.',
		question: 'What did the tenth Doctor tell Sally Sparrow to do to avoid being displaced in time by the weeping angels?',
		answer: "don't blink",
	},
	[2,1,2] => {
		room_number: 14,
		hint: 'You are above, but you need to go below.',
		question: 'What planet is the Doctor buried on?',
		answer: 'trenzalore',
	},
	[2,2,2] => {
		room_number: 10,
		hint: "You're on the wrong floor.",
		question: 'In the current season the Master is known as?',
		answer: 'missy',
	},
}
